What is Data Analysis?
It is cleaning, transforming, modeling data with the goal of discovering useful information 
and useful conclusions with supporting decision making.

Data requirements
Inputs that we need for the analysis

Data collection


Data processing
Structuring of data(does not include cleaning of data)

Data cleaning
removal of unwanted data and improper or irrelevant data

Exploratory data analysis
Seeing patterns and trends in data


HW Q : Make an n dimensional array and print the 2nd and the 2nd last element of the array.