Why selenium

open source and portable 

combination of tool and DSL(Domain Specific Language)

Cost reduction for busniess clients.

Selenium Webdriver is the parent of all methods and classes used in selenium

Webdriver is driving force which allows to perform multiple operation of many elements of webpage

Reduces test excution time
Less resources required
Supports multiple OS, Languages, Browsers

No support for desktop apps